Suzuki.
Do you still read that BL crap?
Quit harassing
our Suzuki.
I'm a fellow BL lover, too.
We've read a bit, as well.
I feel so welcomed here.
I'm having so much fun right now.
Cute!
I've become friends with the popular guys.
- Looks good.
- Suzuki.
- Fried chicken?
- Open wide.
And fried rice, the usual.
Homemade, I assume?
That's my girlfriend for you!
Show off.
Now let's dig in.
So, that set-up was to help Suzuki write.
Makes sense.
And here I thought Serizawa was being weird.
He still is.
Touche.
Now, I can openly talk about BL with them.
Are you actually able to write like that?
Yeah. Bit by bit.
I see.
Let me read what you have so far.
You're not a novel guy, though.
I'd read Suzuki's work.
You know who Suzuki reminds me of
when I feed him?
Usami.
Usami...
Our teacher?
All right, let's start with warm-ups.
Find a partner and get stretching.
He's talking about a rabbit
he met in our first year,
during that field trip we took to a farm.
- A rabbit.
- Yeah.
Serizawa kept feeding the poor thing.
Eventually, it became too bloated to move.
I felt so bad for it
He totally overfed that rabbit.
But it was just so cute.
I wish I could've brought it home with me.
Careful, Suzuki.
This guy can get seriously possessive.
What?
I do not.
Besides, I'm a noble top.
Isn't that right, Suzuki?
"Noble"?
More like, selfish.
- Agreed.
- Right?
Noble, my ass.
But...
Sorry. You had ketchup on your cheek.
It's fine. Thanks.
Sometimes, I get a bit confused.
Suzuki, you're like a twig.
Do you eat enough?
Don't grope the guy.
Eat well, and grow up strong, okay?
What are you, his mom?
Is this something friends do?
Mom?
- He's his Seri-Mom.
- Yeah.
That's a mom for you.
[Episode 4]
Really? Aw man...
All right, who's out today?
Serizawa?
- That's unusual.
- What happened?
- He caught a cold.
- Is he okay?
Yeah. He got the medicine he needs.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
I mean, look at the way he's spamming us.
[The Gang]
Hello?
Dog.
Gouche.
Are you sure he's okay?
He's just playing a word game
against himself.
It's his usual routine.
He's totally bored.
And he lost?
Hilarious!
The classroom's super quiet
without him around though.
[Pudding]
Serizawa's on class duty today?
Too bad, I had a favor to ask.
I'll fill in for him.
I knew if anyone would step up, you would.
Thanks, Takeuchi.
Of course.
Takeuchi.
Suzuki?
I'll help.
Really? Then could you
take the stuff on top?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Did you get a response from Serizawa?
I told you, not yet.
How many times will you ask?
[Serizawa, are you okay?]
[Is there anything you need?]
Something up?
Well...
I was just wondering if Serizawa was okay.
We haven't heard from him since this morning.
Oh no, what if he fainted?
Suzuki.
I don't know if I'm allowed to ask, but...
Do you...
Like Serizawa?
Huh?
Sorry, if you're not comfortable answering...
No, I mean. I do think Serizawa's cool.
But he's only my model top.
I see.
Yeah. Besides, I've never really...
fallen in love before.
Not even once?
You know I'm a nervous wreck.
And I always get really anxious.
So, romance is a high hurdle for me.
I don't really get it, either.
You don't get it, huh.
Then let me ask you this.
You've never felt your heart beat faster
when you're around Serizawa?
What?
'Sup.
Sir.
I've finished up today's logs.
Thanks.
[Class Logs]
Wow, Takeuchi.
You're as meticulous as ever.
Thank you.
Suzuki, thanks for helping him out.
Huh?
Suzuki? Hello?
He's frozen up.
My heart beating faster...
Does that count?
Pinky promise.
What about that?
Here, let me see.
Huh?
Wait a second.
Sorry!
He makes my heart go crazy.
No, no, no.
I mean, sure, my heart rate increases.
But that's because Serizawa is my ideal top.
That's all.
I miss him.
No, I don't!
[Notification]
Suzuki, I want to see you.
I actually came to see him.
[Serizawa]
But he probably wasn't serious.
"Serizawa, are you awake?"
"I brought your schoolwork
and some pudding."
"I'll leave them at the front gate."
"Take care."
Suzuki.
Serizawa?
You really came.
Uh, I...
You can come in.
No one else is home.
Thanks for having me.
This is my room.
Serizawa's room...
And this...
is my collection.
You have all my favorites!
He's got an impressive collection.
Come join me.
Sure.
I'm on Serizawa's bed.
Serizawa's in his roomwear.
Longer sleeves... Un-styled hair...
Wow... he looks so cool...
No, what am I thinking?
Were you able to find my place easily?
Yeah. Takeuchi guided me here.
Takeuchi?
Yeah.
I didn't know you two
were friends from middle school.
He told me you both live near by.
Yeah.
Did you walk here with Serizawa?
Yeah. I invited him to join us,
but he said he couldn't visit today.
I see.
Who did you eat lunch with today?
I ate with the others like we usually do.
Did you talk to any of the girls today?
No, not really.
Why?
No reason.
I was just a bit worried.
Worried?
Yeah.
Look.
I'm glad you're getting along
with the class now.
But make sure I'm always
your number one, okay?
- What?
- Your answer?
Well?
Uh...
Okay.
I'm serious.
What is this?
Suzuki.
Your ears are turning red.
That's because I'm nervous.
Nervous?
You're nervous?
Well, I mean...
Does that mean I make your heart beat faster?
I think, I'm...
Serizawa?
Huh?
Serizawa? Are you okay?
- Serizawa?
- I...
I feel hot...
What should I do?
You're awake.
Did I fall asleep?
Yeah. How do you feel?
First, drink some water.
Thanks.
I feel way better now.
What a relief.
I was afraid you fainted on me.
Are you drinking your medicine?
Yeah.
How's your appetite?
I bought some pudding, if you're hungry.
Did you want any?
I'll eat, if you feed me.
You can feed yourself!
Aw, but I'm always feeding you.
Besides, a weakened top
is good material, right?
I can't deny that.
Fine.
Here.
How's that?
Delicious.
It hits the spot.
What's up?
Nothing, it's just...
You really are like the sun, Serizawa.
The sun?
Yeah.
You know...
I first got to know you
[Year 2, Class 1]
when we were placed into the same class,
in our sophomore year.
Serizawa!
We're all together!
Yay!
I am here!
Yes, you are.
Thanks, Mr. Obvious.
Dude, come on!
At the time, I knew of you
because you had a reputation.
But I didn't know you well.
Until, one day...
Suzuki, you dropped this.
Here.
Thanks.
After spending time in class together...
Suzuki. We're going out as a class after this.
Wanna join?
Sorry. I'm not good at social events.
No worries.
Sorry to put you on the spot.
I realized you were kind to everyone,
without any prejudice in your heart.
Whenever you smiled,
it made others happy, too.
Though school had become a drag for me,
your sunny presence changed that.
So, class today without you,
felt especially lonely.
Aw, man.
That makes me super happy to hear.
Hold on a second.
You think I'm like the sun?
Right, your fever.
Has it gone down already?
I can't tell with my cold hands.
Huh?
Don't pull back, okay?
Seems like your fever's gone down.
S-Sorry!
It's fine.
Thanks for checking.
I'm fine now.
Right.
That's good.
Rest up, okay?
I'll be heading out now.
No.
Don't go.
But your folks... Won't they be back soon?
Nope. I'm alone today.
- Huh?
- Mom's working the night shift.
Dad's living apart for his job.
And my sister's on vacation with her friends.
So...
Stay, please?
I'll be lonely.
Let's sleep together.
[Serizawa]
What exactly is going on here?
Serizawa, I really should be...
Turn away from me.
I don't want you catching my cold.
Hey!
I sleep easier like this.
You're being way too selfish...
Is your heart beating faster?
N-No!
Cute.
Shut up!
What do I do?
This is bad.
Sorry, I'm going home!
No. Don't go.
Stay here till morning.
Until morning?
My heart's going to explode!
Maybe...
I really do...
like Serizawa.
Suzuki.
You like me, don't you?